I guess I'll go home.
It feels like, like there's
something I need to do.
I just can't remember what.
Next stop, Honko Agoe.
Honko Agoe.
Thank you.
Oh, Sachi...
The color of your soul is what
is the color of your soul?
I'm not going to be able to run away.
I'm not going to be strong.
I don't know.
Thank you.
What is that?
It's mind control! Calm down! Stop!
You have to fight it!
That guy's a serial killer!
Snap out of it!
He's controlling you!
He wants us to kill each other!
Dude, you're not thinking straight!
Everyone, stand down and listen to us!
Is he a demon or what?
Don't worry, pal.
You'll be back on your feet real soon.
And I promise to keep the killing going.
Until you decide to.
Why, hello there.
Maybe he'll wake up if I murder you.
I'd have to stop him.
No use.
I can't get up.
Asuna.
It's okay.
You can do it.
Go on.
I know you got it in ya.
Stand up and protect everything you love.
Let's go.
What do you want?
Why are you doing this?
Isn't it obvious?
I want to kill your boy!
I've been wanting to since the first
time I tried on floor five in Aincrad.
I don't think I ever wanted anything more.
You mean you hate Kirito so much that
you would cause all this suffering?
Say what?
A few of all people should
know better than that.
I wouldn't go to all this trouble if I
didn't love the bastard.
The world's full of scumbags, in
case you didn't notice. But that guy,
he's someone you can totally believe in.
No matter how much I screwed
with him or tried peeling back
that honor of his, he never took the bait.
I respected that.
Hell, I cheered him on.
That's why seeing him end up like that,
I'm freaking pissed I wasn't
the one that got to break him.
But I'm gonna be the one
to snap him out of it.
I'll kill whoever I have to and however
many I have to to make that happen
You're sick?
That's why you're doing this!
You don't respect him.
You just get off on making him suffer
You're insane.
Guess I finally got the hang
of how things work in here!
Bet you didn't know all
the spilled blood and
lives lost in this world
get converted to energy?
Back in Aincrad anytime.
I use the old meat chopper here
to kill a monster its stats
would go down But if I used it
to kill a person they'd go up.
Look at it now Here in the
underworld it can suck the energy
from human lives right out of the
air and power up all on its own
Life energy's swirling all around us,
from the American players you killed,
and from the Japanese players
the Chinese and Koreans killed.
And soon as they're
done killing each other,
this place is going to be
overflowing with energy.
My chopper's going to absorb it all,
and then I'm going to hunt down every
artificial flug fight and kill all of them,
too.
I'll start with the Dark Territory, then
murder my way across the human empire.
What do you think, hot stuff?
You think all that death will wake him up?
If he's the black swordsman
I remember, it will.
Don't you worry.
You ain't gonna die just yet.
I'll cut your arms and legs off
and keep you alive for a bit.
I want you to stick around for
what I got planned for him.
To see the big hero waking
up just to die in my arms.
It's okay.
I'm with you.
Always.
Asura!
Show that creep who's boss! You can do it!
I know you can!
You got this, Asura!
Kick his ass!
You...
All you know is hate.
I'll never give in to someone like you.
I'll fight you, to the end!
Oh,
my God.
Thank you, Yuki.
Look out!
His weapon is still
absorbing sacred power!
You'll see that you
still think these people
ain't cheaters now we got
traitors in our ranks!
Working with the Japanese
to confuse you kill
them all and send them
back where they came?
No! Wait!
Don't open it!
Ah, ah-oh.
Ah-ah-ah!
Ah-ah!
Tetsuo!
Uuuug!
Ah-oh! Uuh-uh! Uuh!
You're a beater.
You should have never
gotten involved with us.
Stop it!
I don't want to see this again!
Not again!
AAAAAH!
Stop showing me this!
I don't want to remember!
The pain you caused, Asuna, was way worse!
AAAAAH!
My hand!
Oh, my God.
Aaaah!
I'm the one.
I'm the one that should have died.
Kirito.
Asuna.
Sinon.
Kazuto.
Sugu.
I know you want to comfort me.
Tell me it's okay.
But I don't deserve it.
I failed everyone.
I'm sorry, Asuna.
I'm sorry, Sinon.
Sorry, Sugu.
But I can't stand and fight anymore.
I'm sorry.
Damn it!
What's going on with you, Kirito?
I thought three people would be enough.
I guess we need another person.
Come on, think: who else?
Can we get to link up to him?
Someone whose mental image
is strong enough to fix him.
It's an object from the underworld's
main visualizer connected to him.
Kirito.
Hey there.
Yu-Gi-Oh.
You're alive?
Mama.
I'm the Yu-Gi-Oh that lives in you.
Your memory.
Also, a piece of my memory I left for you.
A memory?
That's right.
Think back to what we told each other.
Remember?
How our memories live forever?
I'm not gone.
I'm right here.
Yeah.
You're in here forever.
Our hearts are what connect us.
So we're always with you.
We're right here.
No matter how far apart we are.
Always.
Even after our last goodbyes,
our memories and feelings,
they are what keep us together, forever.
Is it okay, Yujiu?
Can I...
can I get back up again?
Can I move on?
Of course, Kirito.
Everyone's waiting for you, so let's go.
You, me, all of us, together.
Hahaha!
It smells like roses.
Ha ha ha ha ha!
Enhance armor nymphs!
Oh, my!
That was perfect weapon control.
Kirito!
I waited a long time for this.
Come on, let's dance, Kirito!
Villains!
Oh, my God.
Ito, you're back.
Yeah, I am back.
I love you, I love you.
Thank you.